tractable.io 2017-05-18

# Privacy Policy | Tractable

## Introduction

This policy describes what data we collect about you when you use our web site and how this data is stored and used.

This policy may be updated from time to time so you should check back here if you haven't reviewed it for a while.

## What data is collected

We collect certain information or data about you when you use the tractable.ai website.

This includes:

  * questions, queries, feedback or any other information you email us (including your email address)
  * your IP address, and details of which version of web browser you used
  * information on how you use the site, using cookies and page tagging techniques to help us improve the website

This helps us to:

  * improve the site by monitoring how you use it
  * respond to any feedback you send us, if you've asked us to
  * we can't personally identify you using your data unless you email us

### Cookies

Our website puts small files (known as ‘cookies’) onto your computer to collect information about how you browse the site.

Cookies are used to:

  * measure how you use the website so it can be updated and improved based on your needs
  * remember the notifications you've seen so that we don't show them to you again
  * these cookies aren't used to identify you personally.

You'll normally see a message on the site before we store a cookie on your computer.

You can find out more about how to manage cookies here: [aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

### Google Analytics

We use Google Analytics to monitor visitors to this site. This uses cookies to track your usage, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy relating to how Google uses this data by following this link: [google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

Google Analytics stores information about:

  * the pages you visit on this web site
  * how long you spend on each page
  * how you got to the site
  * what you click on while you're visiting the site
  * We don't collect or store your personal information (eg your name or address) so this information can't be used to identify who you are.

We don't allow Google to use or share our analytics data.

Google Analytics sets the following cookies:

  * **_ga** This helps us count how many people visit tractable.ai by tracking if you've visited before _(expires after 2 years)_
  * **_gat** Used to manage the rate at which page view requests are made _(expires after 10 minutes)_

## Where your data is stored

Data collected by Google Analytics is stored in a network of data centres around the world as described under “Where does Google store my data” on this page: [support.google.com/work/answer/6056694?hl=en](https://support.google.com/work/answer/6056694?hl=en)

All data apart from Google Analytics is stored on our secure servers.

It may also be stored outside of Europe, where it could be viewed by our staff or suppliers.

By browsing the tractable.ai website you agree to us using your data in this way.

## Keeping your data secure

Transmitting information over the internet is generally not completely secure, and we can't guarantee that your browsing activity won't be intercepted and/or monitored by other parties before it reaches our servers.

**Any data you transmit is at your own risk.**

We have procedures and security features in place to try and keep your data secure once we receive it.

We won't share your information with any other organisations for marketing, market research or commercial purposes, and we don’t pass on your details to other websites.

## Disclosing your information

We may pass on your personal information if we have a legal obligation to do so. This includes exchanging information with law enforcement bodies for legal reasons.

## Links between websites

The tractable.ai site may, from time to time, contain links to other websites.

This privacy policy only applies to this website, and doesn't cover other websites that we link to. You should take care to check the address bar in your browser to check if you have followed a link onto a different site. If you go to another website from this one, read the privacy policy on that website to find out what that site does with your information.

### Following a link to this site from another

If you come to this website from another website, we may receive personal information about you from the other website. You should read the privacy policy of the website you came from to find out more about this.

## Copyright

This policy is based on the UK government website privacy policy which is kindly made available under the [Open Government Licence v3.0](https://www.nationalarchives.gov.uk/doc/open-government-licence/version/3/)
